(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-28T20:25:28.752449",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
聖なる夜
Holy night,
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
when four stars become one,
奇跡が、はじまる。
a miracle begins.
さあ
Now,
hyper jumpin' now
飛び越えよ
Jump right over!
ハイになって灰になるまで楽しめな
Get so high till we turn to ash, enjoy it!
hyper jumpin'
雲の向こうまでもっと
Even beyond the clouds, even more!
もっと近づきたいの
I want to get even closer!
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching,
いっしょになれるライブ
a live we can share together!
360度、どこからも。
From 360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly even higher!
ここにいる。
I am right here.
手が触れそうなほど。
Close enough to touch.
2025.12.21 Sun 出演 桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
2025.12.21 Sun / Starring: Nene Momosuzu, Polka Omaru, Lamy Yukihana, Botan Shishiro
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live you can meet in.
聖なる夜
A holy night,
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
when four stars become one,
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ
Now,
hyper jumpin' now
飛び越えよ
Jump right over!
ハイになって灰になるまで楽しめな
Get so high till we turn to ash, enjoy it!
hyper jumpin'
雲の向こうまでもっと
Even beyond the clouds, even more!
もっと近づきたいの
I want to get even closer!
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching,
いっしょになれるライブ
a live we can share together!
360度、どこからも。
From 360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to fly even higher!
ここにいる。
I am right here.
手が触れそうなほど。
Close enough to touch.
2025.12.21 Sun 出演 桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
2025.12.21 Sun / Starring: Nene Momosuzu, Polka Omaru, Lamy Yukihana, Botan Shishiro
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live you can meet in.
聖なる夜
Holy Night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one,
奇跡が、はじまる。
a miracle begins.
さあ、
Now,
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び出そう
Let's leap out!
Come on baby 輝いて
Come on baby, shine bright
ハート きゅんって pump it up
Heart, pounding, pump it up
Hyper Jumpin' 夢の先まで
Hyper Jumpin' beyond the dreams
もっと
More
刺激が欲しいの
I want more thrills
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching,
いっしょになれるライブ
a live where we can be together.
360度、どこからも。
From 360 degrees, anywhere.
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
We want to jump even higher!
Hyper Jumpin' now
Hyper Jumpin'
ここにいる。
I'm here.
手が触れそうなほど。
Close enough to touch.
出演 桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
Cast: Nene Momosuzu, Polka Omaru, Lamy Yukihana, Botan Shishiro
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live you can meet.
聖なる夜
Holy Night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one,
奇跡が、はじまる。
a miracle begins.
さあ、
Now,
Hyper Jumpin'
飛び出そう
Let's leap out!
Come on baby 輝いて
Come on baby, shine bright
ハート きゅんって pump it up
Heart, pounding, pump it up
Hyper Jumpin' 夢の先まで
Hyper Jumpin' beyond the dreams
もっと
More
刺激が欲しいの
I want more thrills
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching,
いっしょになれるライブ
a live where we can be together.
360度、どこからも。
From 360 degrees, anywhere.
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
We want to jump even higher!
Hyper Jumpin' now
Hyper Jumpin'
ここにいる。
I'm here.
手が触れそうなほど。
Close enough to touch.
出演 桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
Cast: Nene Momosuzu, Polka Omaru, Lamy Yukihana, Botan Shishiro
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live you can meet.
聖なる夜
Holy Night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one,
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one,
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ、
Now,
hyper jumpin' 飛び込もうよ
hyper jumpin' let's dive in
入り口だってハイになるまで
all the way until we get high
突き進むんだ
we'll push forward
hyper jumpin' ウンの向こうまでもっ
hyper jumpin' even beyond luck
と近づきたいの
we want to get closer
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching,
いっしょになれるライブ
a live where we can be together
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
We want to jump higher and higher
ここにいる。
Here we are.
手が触れそうなほど。
So close our hands can touch.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one,
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ、
Now,
hyper jumpin' 飛び込もうよ
hyper jumpin' let's dive in
入り口だってハイになるまで
all the way until we get high
突き進むんだ
we'll push forward
hyper jumpin' ウンの向こうまでもっ
hyper jumpin' even beyond luck
と近づきたいの
we want to get closer
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching,
いっしょになれるライブ
a live where we can be together
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
We want to jump higher and higher
ここにいる。
Here we are.
手が触れそうなほど。
So close our hands can touch.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one,
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
さあ、
Now,
hyper jumpin' 飛び込もうよ
hyper jumpin' let's dive in
入り口だってハイになるまで
all the way until we get high
突き進むんだ
we'll push forward
hyper jumpin' ウンの向こうまでもっ
hyper jumpin' even beyond luck
と近づきたいの
we want to get closer
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching,
いっしょになれるライブ
a live where we can be together
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
We want to jump higher and higher
ここにいる。
Here we are.
手が触れそうなほど。
So close our hands can touch.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
Miracles begin.
さあ
Now...
hyper jumpin' now
hyper jumpin' 飛び込もうよ
Hyper jumpin', let's dive in!
ハイになって灰になるまで飛ばしてくの
Rocking out until we turn to ashes
hyper jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper jumpin' all the way across the sea
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A live where we can become one
360度、どこからも
360 degrees, from anywhere
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher
hyper jumpin' now
ここにいる。手が触れそうなほど。
I'm right here. Close enough to touch.
ねぽらぼライブ Re:VISION
neporabo live Re:VISION
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live you can meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
Miracles begin.
さあ
Now...
hyper jumpin' now
hyper jumpin' 飛び込もうよ
Hyper jumpin', let's dive in!
ハイになって灰になるまで飛ばしてくの
Rocking out until we turn to ashes
hyper jumpin' 海の向こうまでも
Hyper jumpin' all the way across the sea
もっともっと近づきたいの
I want to get closer and closer
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching
いっしょになれるライブ
A live where we can become one
360度、どこからも
360 degrees, from anywhere
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher
hyper jumpin' now
ここにいる。手が触れそうなほど。
I'm right here. Close enough to touch.
ねぽらぼライブ Re:VISION
neporabo live Re:VISION
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live you can meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one
奇跡が、はじまる。
Miracles begin.
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper jumpin' now
hyper jumpin’ 飛び出そう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump out
come on baby 輝いて ハート きゅんって pump it up
Come on baby, shine bright, heart goes pump it up
hyper jumpin’, 夢 の 先 まで
Hyper jumpin', all the way beyond dreams
もっと もっと 刺激 が 欲しい の
I want more and more excitement
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper jumpin' now
みるだけじゃない いっしょになれるライブ
Not just watching, a live we can share together
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと高く跳びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher
2025.12.21 Sun 出演 桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
2025.12.21 Sun
Starring: Nene, Polka, Lamy, Botan
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live you meet.
ねぽらぼライブ 参加方法
Live Participation Methods
ホロアースからの参加 IDカードホルダーを購入してライブ会場に入場
Participate from Holoearth: Enter with an ID card holder
ホロアースライブ 開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Schedule
ねぽらぼライブ応援グッズ＋IDカードホルダー付き
Support Set with Goods & ID Card Holder
デジタルグッズ（ホロアースのアイテム）
Digital Goods (Holoearth Items)
ねぽらぼ文字プレート クラッカー 花火
Text Plates, Crackers, Fireworks
ねぽらぼ 特製エモート
Special Emotes
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
Commemorative T-Shirt
ねぽらぼライブ フォトコンテストあなたが公式カメラマンに！
Photo Contest: Be the official cameraman!
奇跡が、はじまる。
Miracles begin.
聖なる夜 4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
Holy night, when four stars become one.
奇跡が、はじまる。
Miracles begin.
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper jumpin' now
hyper jumpin’ 飛び出そう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump out
come on baby 輝いて ハート きゅんって pump it up
Come on baby, shine bright, heart goes pump it up
hyper jumpin’, 夢 の 先 まで
Hyper jumpin', all the way beyond dreams
もっと もっと 刺激 が 欲しい の
I want more and more excitement
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper jumpin' now
みるだけじゃない いっしょになれるライブ
Not just watching, a live we can share together
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと高く跳びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher
2025.12.21 Sun 出演 桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
2025.12.21 Sun
Starring: Nene, Polka, Lamy, Botan
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live you meet.
ねぽらぼライブ 参加方法
Live Participation Methods
ホロアースからの参加 IDカードホルダーを購入してライブ会場に入場
Participate from Holoearth: Enter with an ID card holder
ホロアースライブ 開催タイムスケジュール
Holoearth Live Schedule
ねぽらぼライブ応援グッズ＋IDカードホルダー付き
Support Set with Goods & ID Card Holder
デジタルグッズ（ホロアースのアイテム）
Digital Goods (Holoearth Items)
ねぽらぼ文字プレート クラッカー 花火
Text Plates, Crackers, Fireworks
ねぽらぼ 特製エモート
Special Emotes
ねぽらぼライブ記念Tシャツ
Commemorative T-Shirt
ねぽらぼライブ フォトコンテストあなたが公式カメラマンに！
Photo Contest: Be the official cameraman!
奇跡が、はじまる。
Miracles begin.
聖なる夜 4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
Holy night, when four stars become one.
奇跡が、はじまる。
Miracles begin.
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper jumpin' now
hyper jumpin’ 飛び出そう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump out
come on baby 輝いて ハート きゅんって pump it up
Come on baby, shine bright, heart goes pump it up
hyper jumpin’, 夢 の 先 まで
Hyper jumpin', all the way beyond dreams
もっと もっと 刺激 が 欲しい の
I want more and more excitement
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper jumpin' now
みるだけじゃない いっしょになれるライブ
Not just watching, a live we can share together
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと高く跳びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher
2025.12.21 Sun 出演 桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
2025.12.21 Sun
Starring: Nene, Polka, Lamy, Botan
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live you meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one,
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching,
いっしょになれるライブ
A live where we can be together,
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump even higher!
ここにいる。手が触れそうなほど。
Here. So close I can almost touch you.
ねぽらぼライブ re:version
Nepolabo Live re:version
2025.12.21 Sun 出演 桃鈴ねね 尾丸ポルカ 雪花ラミィ 獅白ぼたん
2025.12.21 Sun / Cast: Momosuzu Nene, Omaru Polka, Yukihana Lamy, Shishiro Botan
会場 HOLOEARTH
Venue: HOLOEARTH
みるライブから、会えるライブへ。
From a live you watch, to a live you can meet.
聖なる夜
Holy night
4つの星が、ひとつになるとき
When four stars become one,
奇跡が、はじまる。
A miracle begins.
みるだけじゃない
Not just watching,
いっしょになれるライブ
A live where we can be together,
360度、どこからも。
360 degrees, from anywhere.
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump even higher!
みなさん、メリークリスマス！
Everyone, Merry Christmas!
本日は「ねぽらぼライブ re:version」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much for attending "Nepolabo Live re:version" today.
ライブ開始はこのあと19時からの予定となっていますので、いましばらくお待ちください。
The live performance is scheduled to start at 19:00, so please wait a moment.
本公演のチラ見せ部分は、動画のYouTubeへの投稿が可能です。
You are allowed to post preview clips of this performance on YouTube.
しかし、他のSNSは音声なしの30秒以内の動画の投稿をお願いします。
However, for other SNS platforms, please limit video posts to 30 seconds or less without audio.
静止画のスクリーンショットや感想などは全編を通じて可能なので、ぜひバイクつぶやきお願いします！
Since screenshots and impressions are allowed throughout the whole show, please tweet about it!
あ、禁止事項ですが、本公演のミラー配信に並びみ音声ありのライブ本編動画の一部SNSへの投稿となっています。
Also, as for prohibitions, mirror broadcasting and posting part of the main live video with audio to SNS are prohibited.
音声なしでも30秒を超える動画のSNS投稿も禁止となっています。
Posting videos exceeding 30 seconds even without audio on SNS is also prohibited.
ルールを正しく守ってライブを楽しんでくださいね！
Please follow the rules correctly and enjoy the live!
ねえ、ねえ、みんな遊びに来る準備はできてるかな？
Hey, hey, is everyone ready to come play?
ねえねえ、大きいタスク着てきている人いるかな？
Hey hey, are there people wearing big costumes?
雪民さんたちがどんな姿で会いに来てくれるか楽しみ！
I can't wait to see what kind of outfits Yukimin will wear to meet us!
ホロアースのライブだから、好きな服装でライブ見れるのもいいよね。
Since it's a Holoearth live, it's nice we can watch in our favorite outfits.
スクショも撮っていいみたいなので、いろんな角度からたくさん撮ってほしいです。
It seems screenshots are allowed, so we hope you'll take lots from various angles.
そう！普通のライブだと、動いて見れて回ったりはできないもんね。
Right! In a normal live, you can't move around or walk around to look.
ねえねえ、みんなの最高の写真期待してるぞ！
Hey hey, we're looking forward to everyone's best photos!
というわけで、ライブ開始までもうしばらくお待ちください。一緒にライブ盛り上がっていこー！
With that said, please wait a little longer until the live starts. Let's get hyped!
hyper jumpin' now
hyper jumpin' 飛び出そう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump out!
come on baby 輝いて
Come on baby, shine bright
ハート きゅんって pump it up
Heart going kyun, pump it up
hyper jumpin' 夢の先まで
Hyper jumpin' beyond our dreams
もっと
More
刺激が欲しいの
I want more excitement
hyper jumpin' now
hyper jumpin'
子どもくらいはしゃぐ方がお得でしょ
It's better to get as excited as a kid, right?
低気圧から抜け上がっていくテンション
My tension rising out of the low pressure
酔いながら打ち返しまくるメンション
Replying to all the mentions while tipsy
カートを乗りこなして進むミッション
Driving carts to push through missions
このままスピード加速して
Accelerating speed just like this
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
I wonder what awaits us at the end
止まらない気持ちは助走つけて
Give my unstoppable feelings a running start
次元を超えて行こうさあ
Let's cross dimensions, come on!
hyper jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump around!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Getting so high until we turn to ash
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing, shake it up
hyper jumpin' 空の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin' beyond the sky
もっと
More
近づきたいの
I want to get closer
(woh...)
ドキドキしたい
I want my heart to race
gimme gimme gimme 愛
Gimme gimme gimme love
もっと
More
高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher
hyper jumpin' now
hyper jumpin'
斜めから攻めて解決クエスト
Attacking from an angle to solve quests
ネガティブを切り裂いてくれるチェンソー
A chainsaw that cuts through the negative
流れるコメントと掛け合いセッション
A session bouncing off the scrolling comments
エイムを鍛えて狙い撃つ flick shot
Training our aim to snipe with a flick shot
dis は no no
Dis? No no
好きなら more more more
If you like it, more more more
邪魔するノイズは撃ち消せ bang bang bang
Shoot down any disruptive noise, bang bang bang
遊びたいだけアンチは無視して
Just wanting to play, ignore the haters
笑い飛ばして踊り飛ばせ
Laugh it off and dance it away
kick it !!
Kick it!!
jump around !! jump around !!
Jump around!! Jump around!!
このまま僕らは旅をして
We'll continue our journey just like this
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
I wonder what awaits us at the end
信じた未来とリンクして
Linking with the future we believed in
次元を超えて行こうさあ
Let's cross dimensions, come on!
hyper jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump over!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Getting so high until we turn to ash
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing, shake it up
hyper jumpin' 海の向こうまで
Hyper jumpin' beyond the sea
もっと
More
近づきたいの
I want to get closer
(woh...)
ドキドキしたい
I want my heart to race
gimme gimme gimme 愛
Gimme gimme gimme love
もっと
More
高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher
hyper jumpin' now
hyper jumpin'
360度楽しんでるかい？
Are you enjoying it 360 degrees?
hyper jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump around!
みんなでジャンプしよう！
Let's all jump together!
斜めから攻めて解決クエスト
Attacking from an angle to solve quests
ネガティブを切り裂いてくれるチェンソー
A chainsaw that cuts through the negative
流れるコメントと掛け合いセッション
A session bouncing off the scrolling comments
エイムを鍛えて狙い撃つ flick shot
Training our aim to snipe with a flick shot
dis は no no
Dis? No no
好きなら more more more
If you like it, more more more
邪魔するノイズは撃ち消せ bang bang bang
Shoot down any disruptive noise, bang bang bang
繋がるコメントと掛け合いセッション
A session interacting with connected comments
止まらない気持ちはぶつけ合って
Colliding our unstoppable feelings
次元の壁を越えて行こう
Let's cross the walls of dimensions
さあ
Come on!
hyper jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump around!
ハイになって灰になるまで
Getting so high until we turn to ash
ダンシング shake it up
Dancing, shake it up
hyper jumpin' 信じた未来通り越して
Hyper jumpin', passing right through the believed future
次元の壁を越えて行こう
Let's cross the walls of dimensions
さあ
Come on!
hyper jumpin' 飛び越えよう
Hyper jumpin', let's jump over!
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper jumpin' now!
hyper jumpin’ 飛び出そう
Hyper jumpin', let's leap out!
come on baby 輝いて ハート きゅって pump it up
Come on baby, shine bright, heart squeezed tight, pump it up!
hyper jumpin’ 夢の先まで
Hyper jumpin', to the end of our dreams
もっともっと刺激が欲しいの
We want more and more excitement!
hyper jumpin’ now
Hyper jumpin' now!
hyper jumpin’
Hyper jumpin'!
子どもくらいはしゃぐ方がお得でしょ
Acting like a kid is more rewarding, right?
低気圧から抜け出していくテンション
Breaking out of low pressure with high tension
酔いながら打ち返しまくるメンション
Replying to every mention while tipsy
カートを乗りこなして進むミッション
Riding the kart and advancing our mission
このままスピード加速して
Accelerating our speed just like this
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
I wonder what awaits at the end of the road
止まらない気持ちは助走つけて
Giving our unstoppable feelings a running start
次元を超えて行こう
Let's cross over dimensions!
さあ
Now then,
hyper jumpin’ 飛び跳ねようよ
hyper jumpin', let's jump around!
ハイになって灰になるまでダンシング shake it up
Dancing high until we turn to ash, shake it up!
hyper jumpin’ 空の向こうまで
hyper jumpin', beyond the sky
もっともっと近づきたいの
We want to get closer and closer!
woah-oh, woah, woah-oh-oh-oh
ドキドキしたいよ gimme, gimme, gimme 愛
We want our hearts to race, gimme, gimme, gimme love!
woah-oh, woah, woah-oh-oh-oh
いぇーい！
Yay!
みんな、元気ー？
Everyone, how are you doing?
元気だよー！
We're doing great!
てなわけで、自己紹介いきましょう！
With that said, let's do self-introductions!
じゃあみんなアイテムとかの準備いいですかー？
Are you all ready with your items and gear?
順番に行きますからね、みんなアイテムの準備してくださーい！
We'll go in order, so everyone get your items ready!
そうね、ポラポラで行くからね！どれくらい待つ？この準備
Right, we'll go with Pol-Pol! How long should we wait for prep?
ちょっと待ったほうがいいか
Maybe we should wait a bit...
みんなスクショ撮ってペンのライブれといてね
Everyone take screenshots and set your penlights!
じゃあみんな行くよ！ねぽらぼのね、みんなの心のエナジーを
Alright, everyone here we go! Linking Nepolabo's energy with everyone's hearts!
せーの！エナジーをひとつにリンク！
Ready, set! Linking our energy as one!
はっじまるよー、ねねでーす！よろしくねー！
Here it starts, I'm Nene! Nice to meet you!
はい、切り替えて！まるポルカだよー！
Alright, switching over! It's Omaru Polka!
いつものないか
Wait, isn't there the usual one?
ポルカおるか？ありやーす！ねぽらぼの、おーまるポルカです！よろしく！
Polka here? Arriyasu! I'm Omaru Polka of Nepolabo! Nice to meet you!
こんみ！ホロライブ5期生の雪花ラミィです！雪花ラミィちゃんです！
Konmi! I'm Yukihana Lamy of Hololive 5th Generation! Yukihana Lamy-chan!
ラミィちゃんしか勝たん！あ、ありがとう！
Lamy-chan is the best! Ah, thank you!
そして最後最後、はい、みんな準備してる？
And finally, everyone, are you ready?
らいやーす！ホロライブ5期生の獅子白ボタンでーす！
Raiyasu! I'm Shishiro Botan of Hololive 5th Generation!
いやーいただきました！皆さんね、ばっちり決まったところで、新しい試みリビジョンライブということで
We got that! Now that everyone's all set, for this new attempt called the "Revision Live"...
詳しいことは概要欄やホロアースの公式ホームページを確認してください！
Please check the description and Holoearth's official website for details!
今日はでもみんながアバターで参加してるし、いろんな角度からのこのりつけ
Today everyone is participating with avatars, and we hope you check out the performances from various angles!
ねねの服を着ている人はいると信じてるからね、みんな！
I believe there are people wearing Nene's outfit, everyone!
いるから！みんなもっとよくくっついてて！
They're here! Everyone group up tighter!
よし、どれが写真撮るんだね！みんなとやれることないかなおまる
Alright, let's take a photo! Is there something we can do together, Omaru?
え、何かな？何かないですかね
Eh, what could it be? Is there anything?
よし、あれやろうあれ！ねえと、走りましょう皆さん！
Alright, let's do that one! Everyone, let's run!
走ろう！ここからね、ポルカが先頭で、うーぐるっと走ってみよう
Let's run! From here, Polka will lead and let's run a full circle!
お、オッケー！じゃあみんな集合集合！みんなついてきてね！
Oh, okay! Everyone gather around! Follow us!
じゃあせーので行くか！せーの、わーー！
Alright, ready, set, go! Waah!
全力で走りまーす！
Running with all our might!
早くしてくださーい！みんなついてこれないよ！
Hurry up, please! Everyone can't keep up!
全力で走ります！全力の本気が来ます！
Running full speed! Here comes our all-out seriousness!
反対半周を返す！送れてる？
Returning the other half-circle! Are you falling behind?
お疲れ様！みんなと走れて楽しい！
Good job! It's so fun running with everyone!
一緒に走れること中々ないからね！ちなみですね、本番の曲の最中ですが
We rarely get to run together! By the way, during the actual song performance...
周りの人がジャンプするとか見えない、見えやすいようにハイよ！してください！
If you can't see people jumping around, please make it easier to see! Jump, pipii!
前寄りの人に配慮して！配慮して！
Be considerate of the people near the front! Be considerate!
はい、盛り上がってる所申し訳ないんですが！
Yes, sorry to interrupt while everyone's hyped up, but...
えー、ここで悲しいお知らせがあります！
Uh, we have some sad news here!
YouTubeとホロアースのエントランスであるホロスクエアでの映像配信はここまでとなります！
The video streaming on YouTube and Holoearth's entrance HoloSquare ends here!
すいません
Sorry.
引き続き、Holoearth ボイスサポートでは
Continuing on, on Holoearth Voice Support,
ライブが配信されますので
the live performance will be broadcast,
YouTubeで見てる方は動画の概要欄をチェックしてください！
so if you're watching on YouTube, please check the video description!
で、チケットを持っている方でまだこっちに来てない
And for those who have tickets and haven't come over here yet,
Holoearth Squareの皆さんはよかったらこっちに来てください。
everyone in Holoearth Square, please come over if you'd like.
えー、というわけで
Um, so with that said,
YouTubeのみんな、バーイバーイ！
everyone on YouTube, bye-bye!
というわけで、次からはソロ曲ですが
So with that said, the next songs are solo tracks, but
まずは、誰からかな？
first, who is it going to be?
誰かな、誰かな、誰かな、誰かな？
Who could it be, who could it be?
ねねちゃーん！
Nene-chan!
それではよろしく！みんなどんどん盛り上がって行くぞー！
Alright, let's go! Everyone, get hyped up!
おー！
Yeah!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!